Guide to the Thomas Michlovic Papers, 1978-2002 AIS.2002.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Tri-Boro Connector/Braddock By-Pass (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Veteran's Correspondence
  - Military and Veteran's General Issues (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Agent Orange (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Persian Gulf War (Box 28, Folder 8)
- General Topics Correspondence
  - Runway Development – Pittsburgh International Airport (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Abortion Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Point Park College Library Center (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Travel and Tourism (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - State Parks Improvements (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - General Braddock School District Merger – Woodland Hills (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Allegheny County House Delegation Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Allegheny County Commissioners Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Michlovic's Testimony to Various Committees – Various Issues (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - North Versailles (Box 28, Folder 18)